Den Brother is a comedy, family, romance film directed by Mark L. Taylor.
Alex Pearson has a lot to learn about teamwork.
As the star of the Lemon Oaks hockey team, Alex almost
always has his way on and off the ice.
That is until he pulls a stunt so outrageous not even
his own coach can give him a pass.
His punishment?
Suspension from the team, a never-ending list of chores and a job
watching his little sister Emily after school.
Alex Pearson, played by Hutch Dano.
Emily Pearson, played by Genevieve Hannelius.
Dina Reams, played by Vicki Lewis.
Matisse Burrows, played by Kelsey Asbille.
Danny "Goose" Gustavo, played by David Lambert.
Rachel Caitlyn, played by Kelly Gould.
Den Brother is a 2010 American comedy-drama film
released as a Disney Channel Original Movie.
It stars Hutch Dano and G Hannelius.
The film premiered on August 13, 2010 on Disney Channel.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.